down-south.com 2001-02-08

# Down-South.com

** **

 **Privacy Statement for Down-South.com**  

**Down-South.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [Down-South.com](http://www.down-south.com/)

**Cookies**  

Our Site uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.  The cookies are only in use on our Message Board which enables you to login automatically.  No other information is collected.

**Advertisers**  

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Personal Information**  

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

**External Links**  

This site contains links to other sites. **Down-South.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**  

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

****

**Contacting the Web Site**  

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
